the-daily.buzz 2018-01-10

# Privacy Policy

LAST UPDATED: 2 February 2017

The Daily Buzz in the United States is concerned about privacy issues and wants you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information. This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with information that we collect through the website owned and controlled by us, or operated by us or on our behalf, from which you are accessing this Privacy Policy (the “Site”). By providing Personal Information to us, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

## UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may change this Privacy Policy. Please take a look at the “LAST UPDATED” legend at the top of this page to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. Your use of the Site following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Policy.

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

### Personal Information We May Collect

“Personal Information” is information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable person, such as:

  * Name
  * Postal address (including billing and shipping addresses)
  * Telephone number
  * Email address
  * Profile picture

## How We May Collect Personal Information

We and our service providers may collect Personal Information in a variety of ways, including: 

  * **Through the Services:** We may collect Personal Information through the Site, e.g., when you sign up for a newsletter or make a purchase.
  * **From Other Sources:** We may receive your Personal Information from other sources, such as public databases; joint marketing partners; social media platforms; from people with whom you are friends or otherwise connected on social media platforms, as well as from other third parties. For example, if you elect to connect your social media account to your Site account, certain Personal Information from your social media account will be shared with us, which may include Personal Information that is part of your profile or your friends’ profiles.

## How We Use Personal Information

We may use Personal Information:

  * To respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests, such as to send you newsletters.
  * To send administrative information to you, for example, information regarding the Site and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies.
  * To send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you.
  * To personalize your experience on the Site by presenting products and offers tailored to you.
  * To allow you to participate in sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions and to administer these activities. Some of these activities have additional rules, which could contain additional information about how we use and disclose your Personal Information, so we suggest that you read these rules carefully – in the event of a conflict between those rules and this Privacy Policy, those rules will govern.
  * To facilitate social sharing functionality.
  * To allow you to send messages to a friend through the Site. By using this functionality, you are telling us that you are entitled to use and provide us with your friend’s name and email address.
  * For our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing new products, enhancing, improving or modifying the Site and our services, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and operating and expanding our business activities.
  * As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

## How Personal Information May Be Disclosed 

Your Personal Information may be disclosed:

  * The Social Edge, Inc. is the party responsible for the management of the jointly-used Personal Information.
  * To our third party service providers who provide services such as website hosting, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment, information technology and related infrastructure provision, customer service, email delivery, credit card processing, auditing and other similar services.
  * To third parties to permit them to send marketing communications to you.
  * To third-party sponsors of sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions.
  * To identify you to anyone to whom you send messages through the Site.
  * By you, on message boards, chat, profile pages and blogs and other services to which you are able to post information and materials. Please note that any information and materials that you post or disclose through these services will become public information, and may be available to visitors to the Site and to the general public. We urge you to be very careful when deciding to disclose your Personal Information, or any other information, on the Site.
  * To your friends associated with your social media account, to other website users and as well as to your social media account provider, in connection with your social sharing activity, such as if you connect your social media account to your Site account or log-into your Site account from your social media account. By connecting your Site account and your social media account you authorize us to share information with your social media account provider and you understand that the use of the information we share will be governed by the social media site’s privacy policy. If you do not want your Personal Information shared with other users or with your social media account provider, please do not connect your social media account with your Site account and do not participate in social sharing on the Site.
  * To a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).
  * As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

## OTHER INFORMATION

### Other Information We May Collect

**“Other Information”** is any information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an individual, such as: 

  * Browser information
  * Server log files
  * Information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies
  * Demographic information and other information provided by you
  * Aggregated information

## How We May Collect Other Information 

We and our service providers may collect Other Information in a variety of ways, including:

  * **Through your browser or device:** Certain information is collected by most browsers or automatically through your device, such as your Media Access Control (MAC) address, computer type (Windows or Macintosh), screen resolution, operating system name and version, device manufacturer and model, language and Internet browser type you are using. We use this information to ensure that the Site functions properly.
  * **IP Address:** Your “IP Address” is a number that is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). An IP Address may be identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a user visits the Site, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that were visited. Collecting IP Addresses is standard practice and is done automatically by many websites, applications and other services. We use IP Addresses for purposes such as calculating Site usage levels, helping diagnose server problems, and administering the Site. 
  * **Using cookies:** Cookies are pieces of information stored directly on the computer that you are using. Cookies allow us to collect information such as browser type, time spent on the Site, pages visited, language preferences, and other anonymous traffic data. We and our service providers use the information for security purposes, to facilitate navigation, display information more effectively, and to personalize your experience while using the Site, as well as for online tracking purposes. We can recognize your computer to assist your use of the Site. We also gather statistical information about the usage of the Site in order to continually improve the design and functionality, understand how the Site is used and to assist us with resolving questions regarding the Site. Cookies further allow us to select which of our advertisements or offers are most likely to appeal to you and display them while you are on the Site. We may also use cookies in online advertising to track responses to our advertisements and we may use cookies or other files to track your use of other websites. 

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to automatically decline cookies, or be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer to your computer of a particular cookie (or cookies) from a particular site. To opt out of Google Analytics, use [this link](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). You may also wish to refer to <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html>. However, if you do not accept these cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of the Site. For example, we may not be able to recognize your computer and you may need to log in every time you visit the Site. You also may not receive advertising or other offers from us that are relevant to your interests and needs. 

  * **“Do Not Track” signals:** The Site will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Policy, whether or not a “Do Not Track” signal or similar mechanism is received from your browser.
  * **Using pixel tags and other similar technologies:** Pixel tags (also known as web beacons and clear GIFs) may be used in connection with some Site pages and HTML-formatted email messages to, among other things, track the actions of Site users and email recipients, measure the success of our marketing campaigns and compile statistics about Site usage and response rates. 
  * **Using Adobe Flash technology (including Flash Local Shared Objects (“Flash LSOs”)) and other similar technologies:** We may use Flash LSOs and other technologies to, among other things, collect and store information about your use of the Site. If you do not want Flash LSOs stored on your computer, you can adjust the settings of your Flash player to block Flash LSO storage using the tools contained in the [Website Storage Settings Panel](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). You can also control Flash LSOs by going to the [Global Storage Settings Panel](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager03.html) and following the instructions (which may include instructions that explain, for example, how to delete existing Flash LSOs (referred to "information" on the Macromedia site), how to prevent Flash LSOs from being placed on your computer without your being asked, and (for Flash Player 8 and later) how to block Flash LSOs that are not being delivered by the operator of the page you are on at the time). Please note that setting the Flash Player to restrict or limit acceptance of Flash LSOs may reduce or impede the functionality of some Flash applications, including, potentially, Flash applications used in connection with the Site or our online content.
  * **Physical Location:** We may collect the physical location of your device by, for example, using satellite, cell phone tower or WiFi signals. We may use your device’s physical location to provide you with personalized location-based services and content. We may also share your device’s physical location, combined with information about what advertisements you viewed and other information we collect, with our service providers and/or marketing partners to enable them to provide you with more personalized content and to study the effectiveness of advertising campaigns. In some instances, you may be permitted to allow or deny such uses and/or sharing of your device’s location, but if you choose to deny such uses and/or sharing, we, our service providers and/or our marketing partners may not be able to provide you with the applicable personalized services and content.
  * **From you:** Information such as your location, as well as other information, such as your preferred means of communication, is collected when you voluntarily provide this information.
  * **By aggregating information:** Aggregated Personal Information does not personally identify you or any other user of the Site. For example, we may aggregate Personal Information to calculate the percentage of our users who have a particular telephone area code.

## How We May Use and Disclose Other Information 

Please note that we may use and disclose Other Information for any purpose.

In some instances, we may combine Other Information with Personal Information (such as combining your name with your geographical location). If we combine any Other Information with Personal Information, the combined information will be treated by us as Personal Information as long as it is combined.

## THIRD PARTY SITES OR SERVICES

This Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third parties, including any third party operating any site or service to which the Site contains a link. The inclusion of a link on the Site does not imply endorsement of the linked site or service by us or by our affiliates.

## THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you access or use the Site. Please note that these companies may use information about your access to or use of the Site and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to the Site, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser (including through the use of pixel tags). If you would like more information about this practice and to learn about your choices in connection with these practices, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> and <http://www.aboutads.info/>.

## SECURITY

We seek to use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect Personal Information within our organization. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please also be aware that we may use third-party cloud service providers that provide hosting, data storage and other services pursuant to standard terms and conditions that may be non-negotiable; these service providers have informed us or the general public that they apply security measures they consider adequate for the protection of information within their system, or they have a general reputation for applying such measures. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us in accordance with the “Contacting Us” section below

## CHOICES AND ACCESS

### Your choices regarding our use and disclosure of your Personal Information

We give you many choices regarding our use and disclosure of your Personal Information for marketing purposes. You may opt-out from: 

  * **Receiving marketing-related emails from us:** If you no longer want to receive marketing-related emails from us on a going-forward basis, you may opt-out of receiving these marketing-related emails by by unsubscribing using the link provided in the emails."

We will try to comply with your request(s) as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that if you opt-out as described above, we will not be able to remove your Personal Information from the databases of our affiliates or unaffiliated third parties with which we have already shared your Personal Information (i.e., to which we have already provided your Personal Information as of the date that we implement your opt-out request). Please note that, if you do opt-out of receiving marketing-related emails from us, we may still send to you important administrative messages, and you cannot opt-out from receiving administrative messages.

### How you can access or change your Personal Information 

If you would like to review or update your Personal Information that has been previously provided to us by you, you may contact us at the following: 

[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

1001 Avenue of the Americas, 14th Floor, New York NY 10018  
[t] (347) 244-7437 / [f] (917) 591-4391  

In your request, please make clear what information you would like to have changed. For your protection, we may only implement requests with respect to the Personal Information associated with the particular email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before implementing your request. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. We are not responsible for changing information from the databases of third parties with whom we have already shared your Personal Information.

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting such change or deletion (e.g., when you make a purchase or enter a promotion, you may not be able to change or delete the Personal Information provided until after the completion of such purchase or promotion). There may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed.

[If you are a resident of California, under 18 and a registered user of the Site, you may ask us to remove content or information that you have posted to the Site by writing to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)cial-edge.com. Please note that your request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information, as, for example, some of your content may have been reposted by another user.] 

## USE OF SITE BY MINORS

The Site is not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13), and we request that these individuals do not provide Personal Information through the Site.

## JURISDICTIONAL ISSUES

The Site is controlled and operated by us from the United States, and is not intended to subject us to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than that of the United States.

## SENSITIVE INFORMATION

We ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive Personal Information (e.g., social security numbers, credit card information, etc.) on or through the Site or otherwise to us.

## CONTACTING US

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), or please write to the following address:

1001 Avenue of the Americas, 14th Floor, New York NY 10018  
[t] (347) 244-7437 / [f] (917) 591-4391 

Please note that email communications are not always secure; so please do not include credit card information or sensitive information in your emails to us.
